Hey.
嘿
&gt;&gt; Hey. &gt;&gt; What's going on?
— 嘿 — 这是怎么回事
&gt;&gt; Just wait for it.
等一会儿
&gt;&gt; Okay.
— 好 — 好
So, you know how we have a variable called number of coffees
所以 我们的应用中有一个变量叫做咖啡数量
ordered in our app.
你知道它是如何订购的吗
&gt;&gt; This box. Yeah.
这个盒子
&gt;&gt; And we had the value two in it.
在里面有一个为2的值
&gt;&gt; Correct. &gt;&gt; If I hit the plus button
— 正确 — 如果我点击 + 按钮
in the app now.
在应用里
&gt;&gt; Beep &gt;&gt; Then
— 嘟 — 然后
what is the number of cups of coffee we have?
我们所拥有的咖啡杯数是多少呢？
&gt;&gt; Well, that would be, increment by one, so the new value should be three.
这样 通过加1新的值应该为3
&gt;&gt; Yeah. So I'm going to
好 所以我将
throw out this old value and put in this new one.
扔掉这个旧的值 并放入这个新的值
&gt;&gt; Okay. &gt;&gt; If I hit the plus button
— 好 — 如果我再次点击 + 按钮
again- &gt;&gt; Beep!
嘟
&gt;&gt; Then how many cups do I have?
那么我有多少杯呢？
&gt;&gt; Well now we will increment that to four.
现在好了 我们将增加到4个
&gt;&gt; Yep. &gt;&gt; So throw this out, add four in.
— 是的 — 扔掉这个 把4放进去
&gt;&gt; Okay. &gt;&gt; Now, if I hit the minus button-
— 好 — 现在 如果我点击 – 按钮
&gt;&gt; Beep beep beep
哔 哔 哔
&gt;&gt; Then how many cups of
我现在有多少杯
coffee do I have?
咖啡呢？
&gt;&gt; But Catherine I thought you said there would be no math?
但是 Catherine 我记得你说过不用算术吧
&gt;&gt; It's one.
它是1
Write that down.
写下来
Thanks. &gt;&gt; Okay.
谢谢 好
Here it is.
这里
One. &gt;&gt; Yep.
— 1 — 是的
&gt;&gt; Let me give that to you.
我给你
&gt;&gt; Thank you.
谢谢
Let's add all of this into our app now and
现在让我们添加所有的这些到应用中
we're going to work on your math later Let's look at the pseudocode for how
接下来我们将进行算数 让我们看一下伪代码
clicking the plus button in the app can increase the number of coffees ordered.
对于怎样点击应用里 + 按钮能够增加订购咖啡的数量
Pseudocode is a high level description that explains
伪代码是一个高层次的描述
the steps of what the app will do.
它解释应用的每一步将会做什么
We can write it out as if we're describing it to someone,
我们可以把它写下来 好像给某个人描述它
because it's meant for people to read, not computers.
因为它的意义是给人阅读而不是给计算机
This helps us put our thoughts into a linear flow of what needs to happen
这个可以帮助我们条理清晰的理清
one step after the next.
程序的下一步该做什么
When writing pseudocode we don't have to follow any specific structure or
当我们写伪代码时 不必遵循任何的特殊结构或格式
format, we just need to include useful details that would help us write
只需要包含有用的信息 这将帮助我们编写
the code later on.
之后的代码
For our scenario, we want to create a quantity variable to keep track
对于我们的场景中 我们想要定义一个 quantity 变量来跟踪
of the number of coffees ordered and we initialized the value to two coffees.
订购咖啡的数量 并且我们初始化为2
If the plus button is pressed, we can update the quantity variable to three.
如果按下 + 按钮 我们可以更新 quantity 值为3
If we hit the plus button several more times
如果我多次点击 + 按钮
we can increase the quantity to four and five.
我们可以增加 quantity 到4和5
Once we have a conceptual idea in our head of what the code should do,
一旦我们头脑中有了代码应该做什么的概念性想法
then we can focus on writing the actual Java code.
然后我们可以专注于编写真正的 Java 代码
At this point then we can worry about the syntax of Java, the capitalization,
在这一点我们不必担心 Java 的语法 大小写
the symbols, the spacing and
符号 间距
other specific rules about how to write Java code.
和关于如何编写 Java 代码的其他特定规则
The real code would look like this to create a quantity variable and
真正的代码看起来像这样 定义一个 quantity 变量
set it to two, we would have int quantity = 2 followed by a ;.
设置为2 所以有 int quantity = 2；
This is what we covered in the last video.
这是上一个视频中讲的东西
To update the quantity variable to 3 we just need to say quantity = 3 followed
更新 quantity 的值为3 我们只需要写 quantity = 3
by a semicolon.
后边跟一个分号
If we update the quantity to 4 and 5, this is what the code would look like.
如果我们更新 quantity 为4和5 代码就是这样的
For this quiz I want you to practice typing out these lines of code
对于这个测验 我希望你输入这几行代码
in the text fields provided.
在提供的文本框中
This will give you practice in creating an integer variable and
这是练习如何在 Java中创建一个整型变量
updating it in Java.
并在 Java 中更新它
Pay close attention to each character and symbol as you type this out.
密切关注你输入的每个字符和符号
When you're done, do you have any observations about the format of
当你做了 对于你输入的代码的格式
the code that you just typed out?
有任何观察吗？
For example, do you recognize any patterns?
例如 你认识的任何模式？
Enter any observations in this text field here.
在这个文本框中写下你的观察